Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 2000 (Box 64-67)
  - Econo-Lite Prod. v. Lahijani 2000 January 10 (Box 64)
  - Eden v. Krieger 2000 August 11 (Box 64)
  - Fed. Bronze Casting Indus. v. Employers Ins. of Wasau 2000 November 02 (Box 65)
  - Fraternal Order of Newark Police v. City of Newark 2000 August 11 (Box 65)
  - Furey v. Bell Commc'n Research 2000 April 28 (Box 65)
    Employment and training programs
  - Gambino v. Morris 2000 April 10 (Box 65)
    Gambino v. Morris, No. 95-4559, 2000 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18498 (D. N.J. Apr. 19, 2000).; No-95-4559, 2000 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 18534 (D. N.J. Apr. 10, 2000).
  - Gomez v. Apfel 2000 March 27 (Box 65)
  - Gonzalez v. United States 2000 October 04 (Box 65)
  - Gonzalez v. Comm'r 2000 June 30 (Box 65)
  - Grabowski v. Vital Signs 2000 August 03 (Box 65)
  - Guckenberger v. Group Reimbursement Welfare Fund, Local 464A 2000 December 22 (Box 65)
  - Haggenmiller v. Moore 2000 July 13 (Box 65)
  - Hanjin Shipping Co. v. Samsung Electro-Mech. Am. 20002202 (Box 65)
    Mexico
  - Harris v. Kinahan 2000 March 21 (Box 65)
  - Holder v. Pinchak 2000 January 05 (Box 65)
  - Huberman v. Apfel 2000 April 18 (Box 65)
  - Int'l Motor Freight v. Yang Ming Line 2000 November 22 (Box 65)
    Opinion; Order Denying Partial Summary Judgment; Order Certifying Class
  - Irving v. Borough of Madison 2000 August 14 (Box 65)
  - Irving v. Sullivan 2000 July 07 (Box 65)
  - ITT Industries. v. Wastecorp 2000 March 16 (Box 65)
  - Jackson v. Moore 2000 April 10 (Box 65)
  - Jacob v. Zavatsky 2000 June 30 (Box 65)
  - Jenkins v. New Brunswick Bd. of Ed. 2000 February 25 (Box 65)
  - Jennings v. Middlesex County Bd. of Chosen Freeholders 2000 February 17 (Box 65)
  - Johnson v. Hendricks 2000 September 22 (Box 65)
  - Ken Smith Motors v. Dilts 2000 October 06 (Box 65)
  - Latchford v. Weeks Marine 2000 August 16 (Box 65)
  - Lawson v. Fidelity Brokerage Serv. 2000 May 02 (Box 65)
  - Leon v. United States 2000 July 31 (Box 66)
  - Lessler v. Vantage Travel Serv. 2000 February 18 (Box 66)
    New Zealand
    Fiji
  - Lidman v. Newark Redevelopment & Hous. Auth. 2000 June 29 (Box 66)
  - Mackerley v. Percudani 2000 July 20 (Box 66)
  - Marchitto v. Connelly 2000 March 20 (Box 66)
  - Marotta v. Drappi 2000 July 11 (Box 66)
  - Martinez v. State 2000 March 22 (Box 66)
  - McCormack v. Sixty-One W. Sixty-Two Owners Corp. 2000 August 21 (Box 66)
  - McKinnie v. Super. Ct. 2000 August 08 (Box 66)
  - Medical Resources v. Bleggi 2000 June 21 (Box 66)
  - Miele v. Digiorgio Corp. 2000 May 19 (Box 66)
  - Mitsui Marine & Fire Ins. Co. v. Blue Anchor Line 2000 May 03 (Box 66)
    France
  - Morris v. Barbo 2000 December 15 (Box 66)
  - N.J. Payphone Ass'n v. Twp. of North Bergen 2000 December 22 (Box 66)
  - Neyor v. Green 2000 June 21 (Box 66)
  - Nikov v. Gregory Park Coop. Corp. 2000 December 12 (Box 66)
  - Norwood Venture Corp. v. Crescenzo 2000 October 05 (Box 66)
  - Paduani v. McKeen 2000 January 12 (Box 66)
  - Page v. Keebler Co. 2000 August 16 (Box 66)
  - Perez v. Citicorp Individual Banking Group 2000 March 13 (Box 66)
  - Pettigrew v. Minor 2000 March 15 (Box 66)
  - Pinker v. Roche Holdings 2000 November 13 (Box 66)
  - Pho v. Hendricks 2000 August 09 (Box 66)
  - Port Auth. v. Affiliated FM Ins. Co. 2000 June 05 (Box 66)
    Opinion; Order │ Order Amending Opinion (2000 June 19)
    Infrastructure development
    Port Auth. v. Affiliated FM Ins. Co., No. 91-2907, 2000 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 20724 (D. N.J. June 5, 2000).
  - Posnansky v. Osen 2000 September 19 (Box 66)
    Reconstruction and stabilization
    Sovereignty, recognition, national governance and status
  - Post v. Aetna Ins. Co. 2000 June 16 (Box 66)
  - Randazzo v. Graphic Commc'n Int'l 2000 December 13 (Box 66)
  - Riel v. Meadowlands Ctr. for the Arts 2000 March 30 (Box 66)
  - Rivera v. Comm'r 2000 July 07 (Box 67)
  - Rodriguez v. Apfel 2000 March 27 (Box 67)
  - Rodriguez v. Reno 2000 May 31 (Box 67)
    Dominican Republic
  - Rodriguez v. Terhune 2000 June 29 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2000 September 29)
  - Scacco v. Metro. Life Ins. Co. 2000 December 22 (Box 67)
  - Schwartz v. Cache 2000 August 21 (Box 67)
  - Scott v. Hendricks 2000 June 19 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Civil Action Order
  - Seibert v. Nusbaum, Stein, Goldstein, Bronstein, & Compeau 2000 June 19 (Box 67)
  - Semeraro v. AGL Welding Supply Co. 2000 August 29 (Box 67)
  - Shabazz v. Morris County Corr. Facility 2000 December 01 (Box 67)
  - Shah v. Comm'r 2000 June 21 (Box 67)
  - Shamsid-Deen v. Twp. of Scotch Plains 2000 February 25 (Box 67)
  - Smith v. Essex County Dep't of Health & Rehab. 2000 June 29 (Box 67)
  - Solchem Italiano v. Bio-Tech. Gen. Corp. 2000 March 21 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2000 July 13)
  - Spellman v. Pepperdine Univ. 2000 August 17 (Box 67)
    Area studies and international education
  - Storm v. Twp. of Woodbridge 2000 June 08 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Order; Letter
  - Tanzman v. Paul Revere Life Ins. Co. 2000 December 28 (Box 67)
  - Teamsters Union, Local 102 v. Anheuser-Busch 2000 July 06 (Box 67)
  - United States v. DeIulio 2000 August 11 (Box 67)
  - United States v. Int'l Boxing Fed'n 2000 January 28 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Order; Order (2000 December 11)
  - Vairo v. Kalvin-Miller Int'l 2000 May 31 (Box 67)
  - Valencia-Gil v. United States 2000 August 15 (Box 67)
  - Vegotsky v. Elio's Bakery & Deli II 2000 August 15 (Box 67)
  - Viojo v. Comm'r 2000 June 03 (Box 67)
  - Visual Tel. Int'l v. Pickens 2000 January 28 (Box 67)
  - V-Twin Mfg. v. V-Twin Holdings 2000 December 06 (Box 67)
  - Warner-Lambert Co. v. Breath Asure 2000 November 22 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Exhibit I; Exhibit II; Order
  - Williams v. Bashir 2000 April 03 (Box 67)
    Opinion; Order Granting Application to Proceed Without Prepayment of Fees and Dismissing Complaint
  - Woods v. County of Hudson 2000 December 22 (Box 67)
  - Worsley v. U.S. Marshal Serv. 2000 April 28 (Box 67)
    Letter
  - Zenith Goldline Pharm. v. Novartis Pharm. Corp. 2000 May 05 (Box 67)
    Adminstrative law and regulatory procedures
  - Zenith Lab. v. Aftec 2000 September 22 (Box 67)
  - Zuniga v. Comm'r 2000 August 11 (Box 67)
    Ecuador
- Papers, 2001 (Box 68-70)
  All papers dated 2001.
  - Amadeo v. Comm'r 2001 September 28 (Box 68)
  - Am. Cyanamid Co. v. Natural Sys. Int'l Corp. 2001 October 04 (Box 68)
  - Angelica Textile Serv. v. Cathedral Healthcare Sys. 2001 October 03 (Box 68)
  - Ardinger v. First Union Nat'l Bank 2001 March 29 (Box 68)
  - Asmar v. Hous. Auth. of Bayonne 2001 December 13 (Box 68)
  - Autronica Marine v. Navia Mar. AS 2001 March 13 (Box 68)
    Norway
  - Avisma Titano-Magnesium Kombinat v. Dart Mgmt. 2001 January 30 (Box 68)
    Russia
  - Bartelstone Glass Distrib. v. TGI Glass 2001 March 23 (Box 68)
  - Bloomfield Partners v. McGraw Edison Co. 2001 August 24 (Box 68)
  - Blue Pearl Music Corp. v. Bradford 2001 June 18 (Box 68)
  - Boyd v. W. N.Y. Police Dep't 2001 March 09 (Box 68)
  - BRM Techn. v. Broadview Int'l 2001 June 22 (Box 68)
    Israel
  - Bullaro v. N.J. Highway Auth. 2001 December 27 (Box 68)
  - Burgess v. Hudson County Corr. Ctr. 2001 April 23 (Box 68)
  - Byrne v. Roman Catholic Church 2001 May 02 (Box 68)
    Historical and cultural resources
  - Cablevision of Newark v. Sklar 2001 May 21 (Box 68)
  - Calloway v. Oxford Health Plans 2001 March 22 (Box 68)
    Calloway v. Oxford Health Plans, No. 97-3946, 2001 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 6839 (D. N.J. Mar. 22, 2001).
  - Centennial Ins. Co. v. Lithotech Sales 2001 February 13 (Box 68)
    Centennial Ins. Co. v. Lithotech Sales, 187 F. Supp. 2d 214 (D. N.J. 2001).
  - Cent. Foods Group v. DFG Foods 2001 February 23 (Box 68)
  - Co-Steel Raritan v. Timberline Transp. 2001 December 27 (Box 68)
  - Daniels v. Pinchak 2001 October 31 (Box 68)
  - Davis v. Comm'r 2001 August 01 (Box 68)
  - DeVito v. Bd. of Ed. of Newark 2001 March 26 (Box 68)
  - Engineered Devices Corp. v. Barsplice Prod. 2001 January 05 (Box 68)
  - Encore Enter. v. Comm'r of Mass. Dep't of Labor & Work Force Dev. 2001 November 30 (Box 68)
  - F.P. v. N.J. Dep't of Ed. 2001 June 28 (Box 68)
  - Fed. Bronze Casting Indus. v. Employers Ins. of Wausau 2001 May 18 (Box 68)
  - Ford v. Sussex County Jail 2001 June 12 (Box 68)
  - Garatina v. DRL Assoc. 2001 July 24 (Box 68)
  - Giancaspro v. Alitalia 2001 October 26 (Box 68)
  - Grabowski v. Vital Signs 2001 December 17 (Box 68)
  - Graham v. Lissak 2001 April 30 (Box 68)
  - In re Grand Court Lifestyles 2001 December 19 (Box 68)
  - Gwiazda v. Comm'r 2001 March 30 (Box 68)
  - Haddy v. United States 2001 February 22 (Box 68)
  - Hall v. Dosky 2001 October 04 (Box 68)
  - Han v. United States 2001 September 18 (Box 68)
  - Harper v. Twp. of Roxbury 2001 July 16 (Box 68)
  - Harris v. N. State Prison 2001 February 07 (Box 68)
  - Hemmings v. Meehan 2001 January 09 (Box 68)
  - High Liner Foods v. LaGalia 2001 July 30 (Box 69)
  - Holley v. Gober 2001 September 18 (Box 69)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 November 14)
  - Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local 863 v. Allied Beverage Group 2001 February 06 (Box 69)
  - ITT Indus. v. Wastecorp 2001 July 12 (Box 69)
  - Journey v. Crown Equip. Corp. 2001 October 29 (Box 69)
  - Kaplan v. Hu 2001 November 14 (Box 69)
    Taiwan
  - Keegan v. St. James Med. Ctr. 2001 June 20 (Box 69)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 November 27)
    Language and bilingual programs
  - Keene v. Cadwalader, Wickersham & Taft 2001 January 30 (Box 69)
  - Khalil v. Otto Bock Orthopadische Industrie Gmbh & Co. 2001 January 09 (Box 69)
    Minnesota
  - Khaliq v. Pinchak 2001 August 24 (Box 69)
  - Kirk v. City of Orange Twp. 2001 June 18 (Box 69)
  - Langley v. Henderson 2001 April 27 (Box 69)
  - Latchford v. Weeks Marine 2001 March 19 (Box 69)
  - Mackerley v. Percudani 2001 March 22 (Box 69)
  - Mann v. Barbo 2001 April 11 (Box 69)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 July 24); Opinion; Order (2001 July 26)
  - In re Morrison 2001 June 28 (Box 69)
  - In re Mullarkey 2001 December 27 (Box 69)
  - Mullen v. Comm'r 2001 March 09 (Box 69)
  - Musculoskeletal Transplant Found. v. Osteotech 2001 September 18 (Box 69)
  - In re Mut. Benefit Overseas 2001 December 06 (Box 69)
  - Nadler v. Applebaum 2001 March 29 (Box 69)
  - Nadler v. Livingston Bd. of Ed. 2001 June 26 (Box 69)
  - Naranjo v. Olson 2001 September 18 (Box 69)
    Cuba
  - Nichol v. Mount Hope Rock Prod. 2001 April 09 (Box 69)
  - N.L. v. Montville Twp. Sch. Dist. Bd. of Ed. 2001 December 07 (Box 69)
  - Pazden v. Terhune 2001 February 08 (Box 69)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 September 06)
  - Pepitone v. Merrill Lynch & Co. 2001 January 16 (Box 69)
  - Pereira v. Farmer 2001 July 10 (Box 69)
  - Perez v. Hendricks 2001 July 09 (Box 69)
  - Petway v. Syms Dep't Store 2001 June 26 (Box 69)
  - Pinker v. Roche Holdings 2001 February 16 (Box 69)
  - Port Auth. v. Affiliated FM Ins. Co. 2001 March 29 (Box 69)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 May 01); Order (2001 May 17)
  - Rejevich v. Comm'r 2001 May 30 (Box 69)
  - Reliance Nat'l Indem. Co. v. Celadon Trucking Serv. 2001 March 19 (Box 70)
    Indiana
  - Remoi v. State 2001 June 29 (Box 70)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 August 24)
    Uganda
  - Rivera v. Cont'l Airlines 2001 June 13 (Box 70)
  - Rosario v. Hadley 2001 February 16 (Box 70)
  - Sands v. Environ Prod. 2001 February 08 (Box 70)
  - Santomenna v. Lors 2001 July 19 (Box 70)
    Photography and imaging
  - Santos Mfg. v. Select Jewelry, Inc. 2001 July 20 (Box 70)
    Metals
  - Scacco v. Metro. Life Ins. Co. 2001 July 17 (Box 70)
  - Schwartz v. Cache 2001 June 29 (Box 70)
  - Shabazz v. Armani 2001 December 27 (Box 70)
  - Solchem Italiana v. Bio-Tech. Gen. Corp. 2001 April 03 (Box 70)
  - St. Preux v. Coach USA 2001 November 30 (Box 70)
  - Sykes v. Hendricks 2001 December 19 (Box 70)
  - Tanzman v. Paul Revere Life Ins. Co. 2001 May 02 (Box 70)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2001 July 19)
  - Teleglobe v. Kelly Broad. Sys. 2001 December 12 (Box 70)
    Technology transfer and commercialization
  - Turner v. Palm Bay Imp. 2001 May 31 (Box 70)
  - United States v. Telephonics Corp. 2001 August 27 (Box 70)
  - United States v. Baig 2001 September 06 (Box 70)
  - Vairo v. Kalvin-Miller Int'l 2001 March 21 (Box 70)
  - Valladolid v. Comm'r 2001 April 23 (Box 70)
  - Vanstuyvesant v. Lloyd 2001 March 09 (Box 70)
  - Vines v. Burton 2001 November 28 (Box 70)
  - Walker v. ITT Hartford Life Ins. Co. 2001 May 31 (Box 70)
  - Weiss v. Stabinski 2001 December 27 (Box 70)
  - Williams Envtl. Serv. v. Akzo Nobel Chem. 2001 July 17 (Box 70)
  - Woods v. County of Hudson 2001 August 02 (Box 70)
- Papers, 2002 (Box 71-73)
  All papers dated 2002.
  - Ahern v. Comm'r 2002 September 18 (Box 71)
  - Ali v. Terhune 2002 June 21 (Box 71)
  - Asahi Kogaku Kogyo KK v. Samsung Opto-Elec. Am. 2002 August 30 (Box 71)
  - Auerbach v. Auerbach 2002 June 28 (Box 71)
  - In re Banicki 2002 March 08 (Box 71)
  - Bishop v. State 2002 September 26 (Box 71)
  - Bronze Shields v. City of Newark 2002 April 17 (Box 71)
    Bronze Shields v. City of Newark, 214 F. Supp. 2d 443 (D. N.J. 2002).
  - Brydbord v. Kash 'N Gold 2002 May 08 (Box 71)
  - Buck v. Twp. of Neptune 2002 June 26 (Box 71)
  - Bullock v. Fed. Express Corp. 2002 June 06 (Box 71)
  - Burton v. Corr. Med. Serv. 2002 February 25 (Box 71)
  - Canfield Scientific v. Cambridge 2002 May 07 (Box 71)
  - Cardile Bros. Mushroom Packaging v. H. Nutile & Co. 2002 August 08 (Box 71)
    Agricultural trade
    Agricultural practices and innovations
  - Cent. Foods Group v. DFG Foods 2002 December 05 (Box 71)
  - Clavin v. Henderson 2002 March 22 (Box 71)
  - Colarusso v. Transcapital Fiscal Sys. 2002 August 27 (Box 71)
    Colarusso v. Transcapital Fiscal Sys., 227 F. Supp. 2d 243 (D. N.J. 2002).
  - County of Morris v. Nationalist Movement 2002 June 21 (Box 71)
  - Cradle v. State 2002 September 20 (Box 71)
  - DeFina v. State Farm Mut. Co. 2002 July 26 (Box 71)
  - DeSaussure Equip. Co. v. Falcon Prod. 2002 November 01 (Box 71)
  - Dunlap v. Leone 2002 December 02 (Box 71)
  - 821 McBride Ave., Inc. v. Borough of West Paterson 2002 June 28 (Box 71)
    Opinion; Appendix; Order of Judgment
  - Emeline Publ'n v. Perfect Ten 2002 December 06 (Box 71)
    Cultural exchanges and relations
  - Essex Computers v. J&J Computing 2002 April 17 (Box 71)
  - Faniel v. Englehard Corp. 2002 July 09 (Box 71)
  - Feigenbaum v. Summit Health Adm'r 2002 August 21 (Box 71)
  - Garatina v. DRL Assoc. 2002 November 13 (Box 71)
  - In re The Grand Union Co. 2002 December 18 (Box 71)
  - Grinblat v. Benel 2002 January 17 (Box 71)
  - Hartz v. Bloomingdales 2002 March 14 (Box 71)
  - Hashemi v. Twp. of Mount Olive 2002 September 26 (Box 71)
  - Howard v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 2002 August 30 (Box 71)
  - Howard v. Nunn 2002 August 09 (Box 71)
  - ITT Indus. v. Wastecorp 2002 June 28 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order (draft, unsigned) │ Opinion; Order | Opinion (2002 October 16); Appendix 1: Calculation Values; Order │ Opinion (2002 December 30); Appendix; Order │Permanent Injunction (2002 December 30)
  - Jackson v. Moore 2002 March 21 (Box 72)
  - Johnson v. Polo Ralph Lauren Corp. 2002 January 28 (Box 72)
  - Jones v. Linder 2002 September 24 (Box 72)
  - Kennedy v. Froehlich 2002 July 15 (Box 72)
  - King v. Hendricks 2002 September 20 (Box 72)
  - Komet v. Republic of Fin. 2002 February 01 (Box 72)
    Taxation of foreign income
    Komet v. Republic of Fin., No. 99-6080, 2002 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 2922 (D. N.J. Feb. 1, 2002).
  - Laurier v. Hendricks 2002 March 26 (Box 72)
  - Lawson v. Fid. Brokerage Serv. 2002 June 10 (Box 72)
  - Lema v. Comm'r 2002 December 23 (Box 72)
  - Lim v. Ashcroft 2002 August 06 (Box 72)
    Lim v. Ashcroft, No. 01-3271, 2002 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21529 (D. N.J. Aug. 6, 2002).
  - Longueira v. United States 2002 December 18 (Box 72)
  - Mann v. Barbo 2002 June 26 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2002 December 12)
  - Markenstein v. Comm'r 2002 June 27 (Box 72)
  - Matesic v. Comm'r 2002 November 13 (Box 72)
  - Med. Soc'y of N.J. v. Herr 2002 March 21 (Box 72)
    Med. Soc'y of N.J. v. Herr, 191 F. Supp. 2d 574 (D. N.J. 2002).
  - Medlar v. Sci. Applications Int'l Corp. 2002 June 21 (Box 72)
  - Melendez v. Dynair Group 2002 June 06 (Box 72)
  - Meyer v. Kent 2002 April 29 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order │Opinion; Order (2002 November 25)
  - Moeller v. Kone, Inc. 2002 April 04 (Box 72)
    Nevada
  - Mullarkey v. Tamboer 2002 December 27 (Box 72)
    Opinion & Order
  - Nivargikar v. Comm'r 2002 August 19 (Box 72)
  - Nkrumah v. Comm'r 2002 June 26 (Box 72)
  - Noe v. Hochberg 2002 December 04 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order
  - N. Jersey Media Group v. Ashcroft 2002 May 28 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order; Preliminary Injunction
    N. Jersey Media Group v. Ashcroft, 205 F. Supp. 2d 288 (D. N.J. 2002).
  - Palmer v. U.S. Att'y Gen. 2002 February 05 (Box 72)
    South Africa
    Louisiana
  - Pascal v. Ashcroft 2002 May 08 (Box 72)
  - Pereira v. City of Newark 2002 January 07 (Box 72)
    Opinion; Order │ Opinion; Order (2002 May 22)
  - Pomales v. Moore 2002 April 25 (Box 73)
  - Preferred Nat'l Ins. Co. v. F. Rodriguez Constr. Corp. 2002 November 13 (Box 73)
  - Propoco v. Jovino 2002 June 12 (Box 73)
  - Ranbaxy-Schein Pharma v. P&L Dev. of N.Y. Corp. 2002 May 08 (Box 73)
  - Riddles v. Ferguson 2002 August 21 (Box 73)
  - Rothwell v. United States 2002 January 07 (Box 73)
  - RLI Ins. Co. v. Brender 2002 August 30 (Box 73)
  - Ryan v. Slater 2002 December 09 (Box 73)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2002 December 09)
    Department of Transportation
  - Samson v. Capital Asset Research Corp. 2002 September 12 (Box 73)
  - Sands v. Environ Prod. 2002 February 19 (Box 73)
  - Sanyei Corp. v. At Home Int'l 2002 August 22 (Box 73)
  - Schering Corp. v. Geneva Pharm. 2002 August 08 (Box 73)
    Schering Corp. v. Geneva Pharm., 275 F. Supp. 2d 534 (D. N.J. 2002).
  - Seibert v. Nusbaum, Stein, Goldstein, Bronstein & Compeau 2002 August 06 (Box 73)
  - Silver Leaf v. Tasty Fries 2002 December 04 (Box 73)
  - Timoll v. Barnhart 2002 November 13 (Box 73)
  - Tobin v. Molesphini 2002 December 18 (Box 73)
    Opinion; Order; Amended Complaint
    Digital media
  - Togbah v. Ashcroft 2002 December 20 (Box 73)
    Liberia
  - Total Car Franchising Corp. v. Wilhovsky 2002 March 27 (Box 73)
  - Tucker v. Roberts 2002 August 23 (Box 73)
  - Tucker v. Walsh 2002 November 13 (Box 73)
  - Tuman v. Brown Chem. Co. 2002 November 04 (Box 73)
  - Turner v. Palm Bay Imp. 2002 November 14 (Box 73)
  - United States v. Allen-Collins 2002 December 31 (Box 73)
  - Willard v. Twp. of Jefferson 2002 September 24 (Box 73)
    Pornography
  - Woods v. County of Hudson 2002 June 26 (Box 73)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2002 November 01)
- Papers, 2003 (Box 74-76)
  All papers dated 2003.
  - Ali v. Terhune 2003 June 17 (Box 74)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2003 June 26); Opinion; Order (2003 December 11)
  - Allure Home Creation Co. v. Zak Designs 2003 July 03 (Box 74)
    China
  - AMB Inst. Realty Advisors v. Enviro-Sci., Inc. 2003 July 02 (Box 74)
  - Bailey v. State 2003 April 17 (Box 74)
  - Baldwin v. United States 2003 December 29 (Box 74)
  - Bohuk v. Barnhard 2003 December 11 (Box 74)
  - Bozeman v. Air Tran Airways 2003 October 29 (Box 74)
  - BRM Tech. v. Broadview Int'l 2003 April 01 (Box 74)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2003 April 10); Opinion; Order (2003 May 07)
  - Bronze Shields v. City of Newark 2003 January 14 (Box 74)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (2003 May 20)
  - Bryant v. D'Amico 2003 January 13 (Box 74)
  - Bullaro v. N.J. Highway Auth. 2003 December 03 (Box 74)
  - Carter v. Barnhart 2003 June 11 (Box 74)
  - Chester Basin Seafoods v. Frometta Consignment Corp. 2003 May 01 (Box 74)
    Fishes
  - Chung v. Christie 2003 June 05 (Box 74)
  - Cintron v. Speziale 2003 November 15 (Box 74)
    Libraries and archives
  - Coe v. Potter 2003 August 28 (Box 74)
  - Daniels v. Thomas & Betts Corp. 2003 March 27 (Box 74)
    Opinion; Order; Appendix A; Appendix B; Appendix C
  - Danvers Motor Co. v. Ford Motor Co. 2003 July 01 (Box 74)
    Maine
  - Domingues v. Amerijet Int'l 2003 January 17 (Box 74)
    Department of Labor
  - Dragutinovic v. Ashcroft 2003 December 29 (Box 74)
    Detention of persons; Border security and unlawful immigration; Refugees, asylum, displaced persons
  - Eastman Kodak v. Hartford Life Ins. 2003 December 22 (Box 74)
    Jurisdiction and venue; Life, casualty, property insurance; Internal Revenue Service (IRS); General taxation matters; Fraud offenses and financial crimes
  - Evans v. Port Auth. Trans-Hudson Corp. 2003 July 01 (Box 74)
    Racial and ethnic relations; Employment discrimination and employee rights; Employment discrimination; Transportation employees
  - Fed. Trade Comm'n v. Check Investors, Inc. 2003 July 29 (Box 74)
    Opinion [incomplete] | Opinion (2003 July 30)
    Federal Trade Commission (FTC); Consumer credit; Banking and financial institutions regulation; Lawyers and legal services; Assault and harassment offenses
  - Fortner v. Unifoil Corp. 2003 January 17 (Box 74)
    Motor vehicles; Accidents; Disability and paralysis; Jurisdiction and venue; Tennessee; Michigan; Mississippi
  - Giglio v. Cohen 2003 July 02 (Box 74)
    Motor vehicles; Accidents; Disability and paralysis; Health care costs and insurance
  - In re Goldstern 2003 January 29 (Box 74)
    Government lending and loan guarantees; Fraud offenses and financial crimes; Corporate finance and management; Bankruptcy; Specialized courts; Judges; Bank accounts, deposits, capital; Banking and financial institutions regulation; Jurisdiction and venue; California; Consumer credit
  - Good News Enter. Inc. v. Edwards Eng'g Corp. 2003 April 24 (Box 75)
    Marketing and advertising; Manufacturing; Retail and wholesale trades; General business and commerce matters; Business records; Contracts and agency
  - Hartford Fire Ins. Co. v. Stallion Indus. Inc. 2003 January 28 (Box 75)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (2003 March 19); Order
    Fires; Life, casualty, property insurance; Manufacturing
  - Hosp. Professionals and Allied Employees of N.J., Local 5004 v. Englewood Hosp. and Med. Ctr. 2003 December 22 (Box 75)
    Labor-management relations; Health personnel; Alternative dispute resolution, mediation, arbitration; Labor standards
  - Int'l Bhd of Teamsters Local 945 Welfare Fund v. Vic & Sons Transp. 2003 June 05 (Box 75)
    Opinion; Order; Judgment
    Small business; Legal fees and court costs; Alternative dispute resolution, mediation, arbitration; Specialized courts; Employee benefits and pensions; Labor standards; Labor-management relations; Contracts and agency; Civil actions and liability; Judicial procedure and administration; Judicial review and appeals; Jurisdiction and venue
  - James v. Ashcroft 2003 January 30 (Box 75)
    Jamaica
  - Jay Cashman v. U.S. Army Corps of Eng'r 2003 March 21 (Box 75)
    Dams and canals
  - Jenkin v. Chartwells, USA 2003 January 17 (Box 75)
    Hearing, speech, and vision care
  - Kelley v. Comm'r 2003 July 24 (Box 75)
  - Ketzner v. John Hancock Mut. Life Ins. Co. 2003 March 05 (Box 75)
    Opinion; Order; Amended Complaint Opinion (2003 March 05); Opinion; Order (2003 November 25); Opinion; Order (2003 December 11)
  - Laborers Int'l Union of N. Am. v. Metropolis Towers Apartment Corp. 2003 October 20 (Box 75)
  - In re Mensah 2003 December 15 (Box 75)
  - Miguel v. Comm'r 2003 February 24 (Box 75)
  - Miles v. Plunkett 2003 December 08 (Box 75)
  - Millett v. Int'l Boxing Fed'n 2003 July 01 (Box 75)
    Rhode Island
  - Morrison v. Greenaway 2003 February 27 (Box 75)
  - Mosley v. Maersk, Inc. 2003 January 13 (Box 75)